{
    "id": "c47372c781be4f21b4fdd759364637e1",
    "title": "Adverbs Of Time",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have known her ................................ a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f1eb16e2b4f4109baa8b4195cad6e1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I once studied the guitar ................................ three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81c7e8e85dab44928075e188c51c836a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been working .................................. six o’clock, and I am getting tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "adf5bba2e6ab4b31a52871a0ce5ad954"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the worst storm ............................... ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "from",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4388a4fe81e4a30bc6d8e6a74e678e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be here .................................. three o’clock onwards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ea4f1c16cc842b9b03d91ce6ffaf3e6"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... now on, I’m going to go running every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "From",
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd0b51f0089d42ae99fe6c4f5283f2b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... the dawn of civilization, people have made war.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "From",
                "In",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "415172c306cd415fa516f0588304712b"
        },
        {
            "question": "By next Christmas, we will have been here ................................. eight years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad47b52e05f24987b3486d7a2c1e21b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think the plane is ..................................... to take off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63cd4d45c1794ddba0f6f61aff837d33"
        },
        {
            "question": "The President is to visit Beijing .............................. May.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a2f197e6fe6f4e3f8315e8fd72b85648"
        }
    ]
}